# SHIBAN AHMAD

MASTERS I N COMMERCE

## CONTACT



**8318352183** 



shiban.ahmad786@gmail.co



Village Pure Karam Kotwa Post Inhauna Distt. Amethi UP 229801 India



O Current Address

Opposite Barclays Building Khora colony Sec. 62 Noida UP 201309

## **EXPERTISE SKILLS**

- · Accounting and Data analysis
- Creative Thinking
- Excel Word PPT
- · Global document knowledge

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Father name: Shakil Ahmad
- Mother's name:- Ishrat Jahan
- DOB:-08/08/1997

#### LANGUAGE

English

Urdu

Hindi

Arabic

#### **INTEREST**



Travelling



**Books** 

# 01

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I started working with Central Trading Company. Worked for two years with job started my Post Graduation, after PG joined Mascallnet India Pvt. Ltd. on 13th of December 2021 and resigned on 10th of February 2023. I also worked with Tech Mahindra for a very small span of time.

# 02

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Masters in Commerce**

Jamia Millia Islamia New Delhi (2019 - 2021)

• Post graduate in commerce

#### Bachelor of commerce

Lucknow Public College of Professional studies (2016 - 2019)

#### Intermediate

The Banyan Tree School (2014 - 2016)

# **High School**

Christ The King School (2014)



#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Tech Mahindra

July 19, 2023 - Current

**Customer Support Executive** 

• Voice process of Flipkart

#### Mascallnet India Pvt. Ltd. Dec 2021 - Feb 2023

#### Executive

- Works on global document checks
- POA proof of address check
- Facial check
- Audits

#### Central Trading Company April 2019 - March 2021

Data operations

- Cash
- Maintaining daily records
- Data entry on computer